payssion.com 2018-12-28

# Payssion Policy

This policy covers how Payssion (“us,” “we”) protects and uses the collected information about the user. Payssion protects the privacy of all users who visit or use the Payssion Service (collectively or individually, "you" or "Users").

The purpose of the Privacy Policy informs you about the information we collect, share and protect when you visit or use the Payssion Service. By using the Payssion Service you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all personally identifiable information collected on the Web site where this Privacy Policy is posted.

Please note if the user is under the age of 13, the user must get consent of a parent or legal guardian to access the Payssion Service. Payssion does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 13 years. If Payssion learns that personally identifiable information of those under the age of 13 years has been collected on our web site or through our Payssion Service, then Payssion will take the appropriate action to delete the information.

#### _Information We Collect_

We will gather personal information about you under the following circumstances:

(I) When you open a Payssion account, we will collect the contact information including - your name, address, phone number,email, date of birth, and other similar information. This information can be reviewed and edited at any time by logging into your account.

(II) When you access our website or visit a web page that using our service: Our service gathers information automatically transmitted from the device(s) you use to access our website or the sites integrating our service, such as your IP address, unique device identifier, browser information, and system (e.g., operating system) information. This information, alone or combined with other information, may allow you to be identified.

(III) When you complete a transaction using our service: During the course of a transaction, you may need to enter certain information about yourself. This information may include your full name, address, date of birth, and details about the payment method you are using.

(IV) When it is provided to us by third party sources in connection with your use of our service: Our merchants may send to us any information you have provided them, including your personal details (e.g., name, contact information) and details regarding your past and current purchases and activity on their site. Additionally, we may receive information about you from the provider of the payment method you use on our service to the extent such information is necessary to process your transaction, or if it later becomes necessary during an investigation into fraudulent or otherwise suspicious transactions.

(V) When you communicate with us: You may need to provide additional information about yourself and your transaction in communication. Additionally, we may contact you to request proof of personal identity, such as a picture of a legal identification document, in order to ensure your transaction is valid or to the extent it otherwise may be necessary to comply with our legal obligations as a financial institution.

#### _How We Use Your Information_

We only use your data for the following reasons:

(I) To offer the Payssion service: We will use your personal information as necessary to provide the Payssion service, including to the extent necessary to process the transaction you initiated, verify your identity, authenticate your access of a Payssion account, and communicate with you about the service.

(II) To manage risk and protect you, the site and the Payssion service: Fraud prevention is a critical part of providing payment services, and we use your information to help us detect and prevent fraud.

(III) To comply with our legal obligations, including all applicable anti-money laundering laws, anti-terrorist financing laws, financial services regulations, and our contractual obligations to the third party partners who provide or help to provide any payment method you use on our service.

(IV) For our other legitimate business needs: We may need to use your personal information in order to enforce our contracts and terms of service and monitor activity on the site.

#### _How We Disclose Your Information Outside Payssion_

Your data may be disclosed to third parties in any or all of the following circumstances. Because your privacy is important to us, we have taken measures to ensure that all of the entities we share your information with have implemented strong data privacy and data protection practices of a level comparable to that which we employ.

(I) When our payment partners need it to process a transaction you initiated: We have contracts with banks and other third party financial institutions for every payment method we offer on our service. When you authorize a transaction, we will transmit to the relevant third party any information they require to process this transaction. What information is required will vary by payment type, but may include your name, address, and details of the purchase you are attempting to make.

(II) When our merchants need it to process a transaction you initiated: Where necessary, we will share certain information about you with our third party merchants to help facilitate the transactions. This data will never include your sensitive payment details (such as credit card number).

(III)When other third parties that provide us with services related to the Payssion service require it in order to provide the services, such as our server hosting providers and independent auditors we engage for the purposes of analyzing our compliance with the law or relevant independent standards. 

(IV) To the extent required by law: We will share your information with third parties to the extent we are required to do so by law. For example, we are required by law to undergo certain routine audits, which may require us to share your information with the third party auditors we have engaged in relation to these requirements. Additionally, we may have to disclose your information when we receive a valid subpoena or other law enforcement request, or when the law requires us to affirmatively notify law enforcement in order to prevent harm or illegal activity. The necessity of all such disclosures will be determined in our sole discretion. For more information on our procedures related to legal requests, please review our law enforcement policy.

(V) To the extent our legitimate business interests require us to do so, for example by transmitting it to our third party partners for inclusion on their blacklists or lists of terminated merchants, to help us engage in our fraud reduction efforts, to support our corporate governance activities or facilitate the sale or other transfer of all or part of our business, or to protect us or our service.

#### _How We Secure Your Information_

Payssion’s goal is to provide you with a safe and convenient online checkout experience. We always protect the security of your information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology for each transmission that encrypts the information you input. All purchases made via a credit card or alternative direct payment must use an SSL-enabled browser. Using SSL-enabled browsers better protect the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is being transmitted over the Internet.When you enter sensitive information (such as e-wallet account details, mobile number, credit card number or your password) and place an order online, we encrypt that information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology which is the approved industry standard.

Users can check the security of their internet connection by looking at address bar of your browser window as you place your order online. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock, then the SSL is active and the server is secure. You can also double-check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https". For credit card transactions, we will securely transmit the entire credit card number to be processed by the credit card company. We will only reveal the last 4 digits of your credit card number when printing an order confirmation. For security purposes we do not keep or store your credit card information as it is only used to complete the secure transaction. Your credit card number and other sensitive information will not be stored after the transaction is complete to help protect your credit card information. To further protect against unauthorized access to your account and to your computer, be sure to sign off when finished.  

#### _Your Choices About Your Information_

You have the right to:

(I) Request that we change any personal information that pertains to you.

(II) Request that we delete any personal information that pertains to you.

To request a change to your personal information, or deletion of your personal information, [contact us](mailto:support@payssion.com).

#### _Use of Cookies_

We use cookies to distinguish You from other customers that use our services or from individuals visiting the Website. To find out more about how We use cookies please see Our Cookie Policy.

#### _Payssion User Info_

Payssion does not and will not, at any time, request your full credit card information, your account ID and password or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited email or through telephone communication. Please never disclose your passwords for any reason. 

#### _Contact Us_

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:support@payssion.com).

#### _Changes to this Privacy Policy_

We may change the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Please check our Privacy Policy periodically for changes. We will post the date the Privacy Policy was last updated at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. The changes will go into effect on the "Last Updated" date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Website, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

Last updated: May 24, 2018
